[{"answer": "I think it started at about 62 when I became single for the third time.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "When you look at this extraordinary life that you've led, when do you think your primetime was?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, to really bring all of yourself, including the not always very attractive and perhaps not loveable parts of yourself to the table in a relationship, to -- it makes you very, very vulnerable.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Well, it was definitely me.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Or was it both?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "That I'm resilient, that I'm brave, that I'm honest.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What have you -- what have you learned about yourself?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "I am -- I'm scared, I'm scared.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "What do you make of what's going on with politics in America at the moment?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I can't answer the question.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "When you look at it, what do you think went wrong?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I don't know you well enough.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Are you blaming me there, Jane?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I think it's been quite complicit.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "I mean, how far do you think the media -- the media has been complicit?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "They all scare me, frankly.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Who impresses you and who scares you?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "I'm worried about anybody getting elected to office who says we have to do away with or privatize Social Security, we have to reduce medical -- health insurance, we have to not raise taxes.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Even -- I mean even someone like a Newt Gingrich or a Mitt Romney, do they scare you?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I hope he gets re-elected.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "What do you think of Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "What do your suspicions tell you?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I think it's a charming camp movie, not very sexy.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What do you think, Jane, when you look at yourself in \"Barbarella\"?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I'm 74 years old.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "I mean, why did you feel -- not uncomfortable, but why are you -- why wouldn't you be that keen to be a sex symbol?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Ava Gardner as a woman.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "-- of all the -- who was the sexiest of all the stars you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "There have been moments in some films when it feels transcendent, when it is the most wonderful feeling when you have entered someone else's reality and you know you're there.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "If you were to tell me what really has excited your passions in life, on a chart list of top three, where would acting fall?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "ONDA: Well, I think the one I'll be remembered for is \"Coming Home\" because it was such a beautiful movie and such a universal -- so many girls have fathers that had a hard time loving them and people really identified with that movie and I think it really -- you know, a lot of people said to me, men and women, but mostly women, I saw the movie and then I went and I brought my father to see it and it changed our relationship.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Which is the movie that if you could be remembered for one you would choose?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I have a favorite, which is -- well, it's \"On Golden Pond.\"", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Which is yours?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, you know, like a -- like a father and a daughter.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "What kind of relationship is that?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "I feel so blessed, Piers, to have been able to have that experience.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "When you look back on that, Jane, what was the experience like for you working so closely with your father?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Well, let's start with the man.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "What would you think the honest portrayal of your father would be as a father?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "I don't see myself particularly as feisty.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "If you were analyzing yourself, what -- how would you describe your character?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, he pretty much knew the way I had turned out.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "But what do you think your father would have made of the way that you have turned out?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you've got to do it.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "How are you going to get me back into shape with this DVD then?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I grew up thinking that if you weren't perfect that no one would love you.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Have you learned to -- to love yourself?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Oh, maybe five times.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "How many times do you think you've properly been in love in your life?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "You -- you couldn't.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Well, if I -- but if I forced you to take one of the men you've loved in your life, who would it be?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "ONDA: I was very, very drawn to her.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "What do you think the biggest misconception about Marilyn was?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Just because one is absolutely brilliant doesn't mean you have to be screwed up.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Is -- was that always going to be the way that someone as genius like but tormented as him was going to go?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "When you look back at it all, with the exception of marriage and the birth of children, what would you say has been the greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I really live for that night.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Are you looking forward to humiliating Anderson on New Years Eve?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "I know I can.", "docId": "111230pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "You could get him off air?", "qSentId": 585}]